Hi everyone. Welcome to our web
application.
This is a demo of how to use the
functionalities of the web application.
Click on new sheet and then add as many
columns and rows you want in the same way
shown in this video.
Note that each cell has a cell name
attached to it, such as A1 indicating a
cell formed by the 1st row and 1st column
and so on. These cell names will be
used for performing all required
operations.
Instead of manually writing values in
each cell, one has the option to use the
copy feature in this manner. Write the
needed value, then assign it using equals
to the copy function call which has
parameters such as the starting range and
the end range. Now use it for other
cells wherever required.
One can find the subtotal in a specific
cell by assigning equal sign to the value
returned by the SUM function. This value
will encompass the starting range and end
range required for the sum.
Similarly for the higher level sum, it
can be assigned in the required cell by
equal sign and passing the sublevel sums
in the sum method.
For higher levels, similarly assign the
required cell with new value and equal
sign to the distribute method, utilizing
function parameters like cell names to
reflect sublevel sums such as categorical
sums as demonstrated in the example.
Now we can distribute these new sub level
sums to find new values for each cell in
the lower levels by employing a similar
structure for distribution, incorporating
all the necessary cell names as method
parameters.
For efficient storage of results, it is
good practice to submit values after each
operation.
The application enables users to download
results in the form of a CSV for improved
sharing and comprehension.